http://www.hudco.com/privacy-policy.cfm

Payment Systems
Small Dollar Lending and Alternative Consumer Financial Services
Payment Systems
Small Dollar Lending and Alternative Consumer Financial Services
Introduction
This Privacy Policy describes the information that we collect through our website and how we use that information. If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
The Information That We Collect and How We Use It
Hudson Cook, LLP collects no personally identifying information (such as your name, address, email address, etc.) about you as you visit our website.
Our web server automatically logs certain information such as the IP address of the computer you are using to connect to our website, the type of browser software and operating system installed on the computer, the date and time you access our website and the website address, if any, from which you linked directly to our website. We use this log information in aggregate to study visitors' traffic patterns, which helps us to improve the usability of our website. We do not use such data in any way to create or maintain a personal profile of you or collect personal information from you.
We will not disclose information we collect through your use of the website to third parties, except as may be legally required.
Use of Cookies
We use "cookies" to collect information about your use of the website. The information collected is not personally identifying information but rather basic information about your connection to the Internet - e.g., session identifiers so that we may deliver website content to you consistently throughout your visit.
Revisions to Privacy Policy
Hudson Cook, LLP reserves the right to revise this Privacy Policy at any time. Your use of our website constitutes your acceptance of the terms of the Privacy Policy as amended or revised by us.
Links to Other Websites
This website contains links to other websites from time to time. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other websites. This Privacy Policy applies solely to the information which we collect through this website.
Opens in a new window
Opens an external site
